

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2021 - Present day (~2 years) • Remote

ARK ECOSYSTEM - FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

I work remotelxy as a Full-Stack Software Developer for Ark **Ecosystem**, where I have been one of the top contributors to his different blockchain-related products and technologies. Those projects include ArkVault, MSQ, ArkScan and ArkLauncher within other tools and libraries.

May 2018 - Oct 2021 (~2 years) •

SURG.IO - FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

I worked remotely as a Full Stack Software Developer for <u>Surgio</u> where, as the top contributor on the project during my time there, I helped to increase the user experience by completely renovating the front with all kinds of custom Vue components, improving the overall workflow, implemented a lot of new features in the backend and worked with the team to standardize and enhance the application codebase.

Feb 2009 - Dic 2019 (~10 years) • Mexico City

VEXILO - FOUNDER & DEVELOPER

I established the company <u>Vexilo</u>, where, for more than ten years, I developed and managed over 50 successful websites and web applications for a wide variety of companies in Mexico. In addition, as the company owner, I had the opportunity to acquire a lot of experience leading teams, creating positive relationships with clients, and general business management.

Aug 2007 - Jan 2009 (~2 years) • Mexico City

INGENIA AGENCY - FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

While still in college, I was the youngest employee of **Ingenia** Agency, one of the top digital agencies in Mexico City. While working there, I had the opportunity to work and, in some cases, lead some projects for some of the most important companies in Mexico City, like Brother Mexico, Coca-Cola, Megacable, and many more.

CONTACT INFORMATION

- ✓ alfonso@vexilo.com
- @alfonsobries
- @alfonsobries
- in /alfonsobribiesca



SKILLS & KNOWLEDGE

I AM AN EXPERT IN:

The following is a list of the different technologies where I have a deep. [More...]

FRAMEWORKS & TOOLS

- ✓ Laravel
- √ VueJs
- ✓ React
- React Native
- ✓ Redux
- ✓ Next.js
- ✓ Alpine.js
- ✓ Nuxt|S
- ✓ Vuex
- Tailwind
- ✓ Bootstrap

PROGRAMIC LANGUAGES

- ✓ PHP
- ✓ SQL
- ✓ JS
- ✓ TypeScript

OTHER TECHS & METHODOLOGIES

- MySQL/PostgreSQL
- ✓ Redis
- ✓ TDD
- ✓ Restful APIs
- ✓ Jest
- Mocha
- ✓ Vitest
- ✓ Scrum
- ✓ CI
- ✓ Github Actions
- ✓ Sass/Less/Stylus



OPEN SOURCE & PERSONAL PROJECTS

Linux Servers

VISIT MY WEBSITE

Visit the Labs section on my personal website, the online <u>version</u> of this resume or explore my <u>Github profile</u> to check some of my open-source tools, side-projects, and experiments.



https://www.alfonsobries.com/



EDUCATION

Feb 2014 - Ene 2018 (4.5 years) • Online

LA SALLE UNIVERSITY - BACHELOR OF SYSTEMS **ENGINEERING**

I have a software engineering degree from La Salle University, one of the most recognized private universities in Mexico. In my undergraduate studies, I acquired one of the highest grades of my generation, placing me in the top 10%.

Continual • Online

ONLINE COURSES & SELF LEARNING

During the last years, I have been taking online courses and reading books to keep my skills up to date. I have also been working on personal projects to learn new technologies and improve my skills. Visit the online version of this resume for details.

I HAVE STRONG KNOWLEDGE

I have worked with the following technologies over the last several years. Howev [More...]

FRAMEWORKS & TOOLS

- ✓ Web3
- ✓ Solidity

TECHS & METHODOLOGIES

- ✓ Blockchain
- ✓ GraphQL
- ✓ Docker
- ✓ Elastic Search
- ✓ AWS
- ✓ Electron

S

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm Alfonso. For the past 15 years, I have been building and designing software for a wide variety of businesses, either working in my company In Mexico or, in recent years, working as a member of different companies worldwide. My specialty is full-stack architecture and development, and, as you can see in my resume, I am proficient in several technologies.

In my spare time, I enjoy traveling, reading a good book, watching a good TV series, playing with my kids, and I recently started training for triathlons.

[More...]